Hello.
こんにちは
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いですね
Isn't that often said?
よく言われないですか?
I won't be told.
言われないです
That's because of the person's answer.
それはね、言われてる人の答えからです
After being told so many things, I felt like enough was enough.
散々言われて、もういいよって感じが
That's amazing, aren't you some kind of idol?
すごいね、なんかアイドルになってないですか?
What do you think?
どうです?
What's the path over there?
そっちの道は?
Well,
でね、
It's really super cute.
本当 にめちゃくちゃ可愛い
By the way, what do you do to post these now?
ちなみに今は何して貼る人なんですか?
I'm a bar clerk.
居酒屋の店員です
Is there such a cute bar employee?
こんな可愛い居酒屋の店員いてます?
What would you do if a customer asked you something?
お客さんに何か言い寄られたらしないですか?
I don't.
しないです
not at all?
全然?
That's a little problematic.
ちょっとそれは問題ありですね
Are you actually dating a bar worker?
実は居酒屋の店員と付き合ってるとかないんですか?
No.
ないです
It's because it's really tight.
本当に引き締まったからだね
Is that something?
なんか あれですか?
Did you join the sports club or something?
運動部とかに乗ったとかですか?
When I was in high school, I was on the track and field team.
高校の時、陸上部でした
It’s out!
出た!
Track and field club!
陸上部!
What kind of event is that?
それは種目で言うとどんなんですか?
It was a long trip.
長距離してました
How many kilometers is considered long distance?
長距離って何キロぐらいから長距離って言うんですか?
I think it starts from 1.5km.
1.5キロからだと思います
Did you only drive 1,500km?
1,500キロだけ走ってたんですか?
1,500 km and 3,000 km.
1,500キロと3,000キロ
That's amazing.
すごいな
I was able to run 1,500km now.
今1,500キロも走れてた
It's not great, but I can't run.
とてもでないけど走れないですね
Can you still run?
今でも走れます?
I'll run.
走ります
That's amazing.
すごいな
That's right.
そりゃそうですよ
I feel like I can run for many meters since I'm so toned.
こんだけ引き締まったからだと何メートルでも走れそうですよ
There were only about 3 floors of stairs.
階段の3階ぐらいもなかっただけで、
My uncle is saying the wrong thing.
おじさんはずれて言ってるんで
I see.
そうか
Oh no, it's cute.
いやいや、かわいいな
That's amazing.
すごいな
I often hear this from everyone,
これ皆さんによく聞いてるんですけども、
How old were you when you had your first experience?
初体験は何歳ですか?
It was during my second year of high school.
高校2年生の時です
17 years old?
17歳?
6 years old?
6歳?
17 years old.
17歳
What kind of person is the other person?
相手はどんな人ですか?
He was kind.
優しかったです
Boyfriend at the time?
当時の彼氏?
Or maybe he wasn't a boyfriend at all.
それとも全然彼氏じゃなかったのに
It's my boyfriend.
彼氏です
Are you your boyfriend?
彼氏ですか?
Where is it?
場所は?
Of my boyfriend.
彼氏のうち
How was it?
どうでした?
After the first time, do you feel like this is what you became as an adult?
初めての終わった後、これが大人になったのか的な感じですか?
Or this one?
それとも、このもん?
Like.
みたいな
This thing.
このもん
That's right.
そうなんだ
Didn't it hurt?
痛くはなかったですか?
It hurts, but I owned the land several times before I finally did it.
痛く、最後にするまでに何回か土地オーナーしてて
Ah, it happened often.
あ、よくありましたよね
At first, it seems like no matter what we both try for the first time, it doesn't go well.
初っ端、お互い初めてどうしようと上手くいかないパターンみたい
That's a good thing, isn't it?
な やつですよね
So, to some extent, there was a certain amount of cross-dressing, or rather, a foreshadowing.
じゃあ、ある程度、女装というか前振りがあったんです
Not so much.
さほどそんな
It didn't hurt too much.
あんまり痛くなかった
That's right.
そうなんですね
I see.
そうか
What do you think?
どうですか?
Looking back now, what are my memories of that time?
今振り返って、その時の思い出としては
Nothing.
なんもない
When it comes to meeting someone for the first time, I think it's very memorable.
初めての相手というと、すごく記憶に残っているのかなと思うん
But.
です けど
Do you still remember?
まだ思い出すことありますか?
No.
ないです
It's quite messy.
結構ざばざばしてるね
I see.
そうか
So, I'm asking everyone this,
じゃあ、これをみんなに聞いているんですけど、
I had that first experience, and I think a lot of things happened after that.
そういう初体験があって、その後いろいろあったと思うんです
But, maybe I was a pervert?
けど、 これ私、変態だったんちゃうか?
Are there any similar plays?
みたいなプレイとか、そういったありますか?
Hmm, maybe not.
うーん、ないかも
But I went to buy toys with my company.
でも、会社と一緒におもちゃ買いに行きました
Would you like to go with me to the store?
それ一緒に行って、お店に?
that's right.
そうです
That's pretty good.
それ、なかなかあれですね
Are you going to an adult shop next?
続にアダルトショップにですか?
that's right.
そうです
When a girl walks into an adult shop,
アダルトショップに女の子が入ってきたら、
This one will pull.
こっちが引きますよ
When I said I was a customer, wow.
僕がお客さんって言ったら、うわ、
I was like, why are you wearing it with a cup?
なんでカップで着てるやん、みたいな
Why did you wear that together?
それはなんで一緒に着ていったんですか?
Somehow, the flow of the story made me want to go.
なんか、話の流れでそうなって、行こうってなりました
Don't girls usually dislike it in such cases?
普通、女の子そういう場合、嫌がらないんですか?
You don't like it or you don't like it?
嫌やーとか、嫌がらないんですか?
I didn't like it when I was free.
フリーでは嫌がりました
Ah, actually, I'm curious.
あ、実はでも興味津々
yes.
はい
How did you feel going into an adult shop for the first time?
どうでした、初めてアダルトショップに入った感想は?
I felt nervous and embarrassed.
なんか、緊張して、恥ずかしくて、
It came out right away.
すぐ出ました
What did you buy?
何を買ったんですか?
Well, my boyfriend bought it.
なんか、彼氏が買ってました
What did you buy?
何を買ったんですか、それは?
Not good.
よくない
I didn't use it, but I was embarrassed.
使わなかったんですけど、恥ずかしくて
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Didn't you repeat it so much?
めちゃめちゃリピートしとったんじゃない?
I don't really use it.
それは本当に使ってない
I haven't used it.
使ってない
I see.
そうか
Is there anything else?
他はないですか?
That's about it.
それぐらいです
For example, it was often outside.
なんか、例えば、よくあるのは外であったとか、
Isn't there?
ないですか?
Now I have my choice of bed.
もう、ベッド一択
Yeah.
うん
So, on the other hand, wouldn't you like to try something like this?
じゃあ、逆にちょっとこんなんしてみたいなってのはないですか?
Wishfully.
願望的に
do not have.
ない
I feel like I'm grinning right now,
なんか、今のニヤニヤしてる感じから、
Were you thinking about something just now?
何か今、思ってたでしょ?
No.
ないです
You see, there are things that are good for men and things that are good for women, right?
ほら、男性にいいとか、女性にいいとかあるじゃないですか?
How about that?
それはどうですか?
No.
ないです
Now it's one on one.
もう、一対一
Now I want to stab it.
もう、刺しでいきたいと
That's right.
そうだ
When I asked quite a few women, they said it was good for men.
結構、女性に聞いてたら、やっぱり男性にいいとかに、
There are a lot of kids who just want to get stabbed like this.
ちょっとこう、一緒にいっぱい刺されられたいっていう子が多
So I was wondering what to do.
かった んで、どうかなと思ったんですけど
I am normal.
私はノーマルと
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
is that so.
そうですか
Judging by the way he grins, it looks like something will happen if he closes it.
そのニヤキ方からすると、締めたら何かがありそうですよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What do you think?
どうですか?
What do you think of yourself as a pervert?
自分では変態的な、度数的にはどう思います?
But I think it's normal.
でも、普通だと思います
Ah, normal.
あ、普通
But I wonder what's normal.
でも、何が普通かって思うね
surely.
確かに
Yes, there is.
ありますもんね
Maybe what your sister thinks is normal,
ひょっとしたらね、お姉さんが思っている普通が、
From my point of view, I think he's a bit of a pervert.
僕から見たら、ド変態やんけってこともある
Maybe I can see your face,
もしかしてね、お顔が見えるように、
Nearby.
近くに
Could you please turn towards me for a moment?
ちょっとこっち向いてもらっていいですか?
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いな
But my face is too small.
でも、顔が小さすぎる
Isn't that often said?
よく言われないですか?
It is said.
言われます
Ah, that's what I'm told.
あ、それは言われるんだ
That's what I say.
それは言うよね
Is it a little dazzling?
ちょっと眩しいですか?
Her legs are also thin.
足も細い
My arms are also thin.
腕も細いけど
Where is the part of yourself that is confident?
自分の中で自信のあるパーツはどこありますか?
Is there actually one?
実はあるんでしょ?
do not have.
ない
Isn't there?
ないか
Wait a minute, do you mean you hold it with a button?
ちょっとじゃあね、それって、ボタンで握るの?
It's all connected.
全部繋がってます
Can I get your belt first?
まずベルト取ってもらっていいですか?
Ah, that's what it means.
あ、そういうことなんですね
Please turn to the side for a moment.
ちょっと横に向いてもらって
That's nice.
いいですね
May I ask you to remove those two buttons?
そのボタンを2つほど取ってもらってもいいですか?
What happened?
どうしたんですか?
I'm having trouble with my face.
顔が困ってますよ
Uncle, do you think I shouldn't touch you?
おじさん、触るなよって思ってるんですか?
What do you think?
どうなんですか?
I want you to touch me.
触ってくれと
Wait a minute, can you get your arm out of this?
ちょっと これ、腕抜けますか?
It's so thin.
細いなぁ
As expected.
さすが
The tip is already a little stiff.
なんか先っちょがもうすでにちょっと硬いんですけど
Is it just my imagination?
気のせいですか?
Look, it's not just my imagination.
ほら、気のせいじゃないですよね
What do you think?
どうなんですか?
What happened?
どうしたんですか?
tickles.
くすぐったい
Is it ticklish?
くすぐったいか
You feel that way, right?
的な感じてるんでしょ?
different?
違う?
Yeah.
うん
What happened?
どうしたんですか?
I'm touching something though.
なんか触ってますけど
Revenge?
仕返し?
Let's make a little noise.
ちょっとじゃあ騒げましょうかな
Don't you feel like it's getting hard?
硬くなってきた感じしませんか?
What do you think?
どうですか?
What are you going to do?
どうするんですか?
Can I take it off?
脱がしていいですか?
of course.
もちろん
Take it off.
脱がして
This cute girl is masturbating her uncle's dick.
こんな可愛い子が、おじさんのおちんちんをまさくってる
How do you like it, uncles?
いかがですか、おじさんらは?
What are you going to do after this?
このあとどうするんですか?
Take off.
脱がる
Oh, this too?
あ、これも?
yes.
はい
I took it off.
脱いちゃいましたよ
What are you going to do with this?
どうするんですか、これ?
I can't get into your uncle's penis.
入らないな、おじさんのおちんちんを
Do you want to try something a little too dark and sparkly?
ちょっと裏すぎて、キラキラってやってみたいですか?
Hand line here.
こっちに手線を
Do not rub the balls with your left hand.
左手で玉をすりません
Wow, that's great.
わー、最高
Just barely.
ギリギリ
do you understand?
わかりますか?
It's too backwards.
裏すぎますよ
Oh, it looks like it's looking at the camera.
あ、カメラ目線に見えます
An old man with boobs is watching,
おっぱいのおじさんが見てますけど、
How are you feeling?
どんな気分ですか?
Hehehehe.
うふふふ
I want everyone to give it a lot.
みんな、いっぱい出してほしい
Oh yeah, looking at the camera.
そうそうそう、カメラ目線
There
そこ
That looks amazing.
そ こ、すごいっちゃいそう
It comes out in your mouth.
お口の中で出すよね
What are you going to do?
どうするんですか?
One more time, calm down.
ちょっともう一回、安定して
Be a little more stable.
もう少し安定して
What happened to your uncle's coin?
どうでしたっけ、おじさんのコインは?
cute.
かわいい
I reconsidered my uncle's spirit.
おじさんの精神を見直した
Could you please shift that dress a little bit?
ちょっとそのワンピースとか、それをずらしてもらっていい
Is it?
ですか?
Just a moment, tighten.
ちょっと こう、ギュッと
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Yeah.
うん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
So next time, can I take off my pants?
じゃあ次はパンツを脱いでもいいですか?
Ah, I see.
あ、なるほどですね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいですか?
So, do you want to take it off?
じゃあ、脱ぎますか
It feels like it's stretching around there, so I'd like you to take a shower.
そ こら辺が伸びている感じで、シャワーを持ってもらっていい
Is it?
ですか?
I thought it was home.
お うちだと思って
I can't wear clothes at home.
おうちは服を着れないからね
Is it home?
家ですか?
Yes, yes.
はいはい
It's like a normal house.
普段通りの家みたいな
So, is this good too?
じゃあ、こっちもいい?
yes.
そう
Which one is better, like Uton's house?
うとんの家とか、どっちがいいですか?
This is it.
これだ
Hey, put on some volume sports.
ちょっと、ボリュームポーツをつけて
yes.
はい
Oh, it was so cold.
あー、あんまり寒かった
Shikrem, can I have you raise your thighs?
シクレム、お股が上がってもらっていいですか?
What do you think?
どうですか?
Can I have you sit there for a second?
ちょっと、そこに座ってもらっていいですか?
yes.
はい
Again, even if I try to show off.
またね、気を出せようとしても
Is there anything important happening lately?
最近、大事なことないですか?
Oh, that makes sense.
お、気が通って
attacked.
攻撃された
thank you.
ありがとうございます
please.
お願いします
Can I use it as is?
このまま使ってもらっていいですか?
It's disgusting.
気持ち悪いです
Oh, do you like Ten-chan?
あ、てんちゃん好きなんですか?
There are three.
3つです
Like I said, I love you.
言ってもた好きってことで
What do you like about Ten-chan?
どんなの、てんちゃんが好きですか?
There are three.
3つです
I'm planning.
企んでる
Because I'm really healthy.
めっちゃ元気であるから
Yeah.
うん
Do you like Genki Ten-chan?
元気のてんちゃんは好きですか?
It's disgusting.
気持ち悪いです
気持ち悪いな
feel ill.
気持ち悪い
Yeah.
うん
While playing with the ball in his left hand.
左手に球をさわさわしながら
Are you starting to want some?
ちょっと欲しくなってきましたか?
How was it?
どうでした?
Oh, that turned on.
あ、そこはオンになった
Well then, please stand up.
じゃあね、その後、立ってもらって
Let me help you.
手をついてもらって
Should you stick your butt out?
お尻を突き出すか
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
May I?
いいですか?
Do you know how to use it?
使い方わかりますか?
Oh, I don't know.
え、わかんないです
There are two buttons, right?
2つボタンあるでしょ?
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
Even if you press the bottom.
それ一番下を押しても
Eh.
えー
Where do you put it?
それをどこに当てるんですか?
I don't know.
わかんないです
You understand, right?
わかってるでしょ?
Please hit this wherever you like.
この 好きなところに当ててみてください
No, no, no.
違う違う違う
That blur isn't there.
そのボケはいない
That's a nice blur, it's my first time seeing it.
いいボケやな、初めてのボケやわ
Where do you put it?
どこに当てるんですか?
I don't know.
わかんないです
You went to Atart Shop with your boyfriend to check it out, right?
彼氏とアタルトショップ行って見てきたんでしょ?
Yeah yeah yeah.
うんうんうん
What do you think?
どう ですか?
Do you understand?
わかりましたか?
I don't know.
わかんないです
My uncle.
おじさんがね
Could you please push me a little more?
もうちょっと押してもらっていいですかね
This is how you use it.
こうやって使うんですよ
I learned this for the first time.
初めて知った
Yeah yeah yeah.
うんうんうん
May I?
いいですか?
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
Wherever you like.
自分で好きなところで
What do you think?
どうですか?
Does it feel good?
いい感じ?
Yeah.
うん
Can I get some hair removed?
ちょっと髪の毛を剥いてもらっていいですか?
I'm really stripping it out of my hair though.
めっちゃ髪の毛から剥いてるけど
It's embarrassing to do it myself.
自分ですんのは恥ずかしい
Sorry.
すいません
What do you think?
どうですか?
It's pretty good.
結構いいですよ
Oh no.
やば
I feel like I'll live a little longer.
もう少し生きそうな気がする
Oh no.
やば
Do you not like it?
嫌なの?
Yeah.
うん
Is the previous one better?
さっきのほうがいい?
Yeah.
うん
I don't like it.
嫌
Do you want it already?
もう欲しいの?
Yeah.
うん
tired.
疲れた
I guess I'm starting to want it.
欲しくなってきたんだね
What do you think?
どうなんですか?
I used it.
使いました
You want it, right?
欲しいんでしょ?
I used it.
使いました
You want it, right?
欲しいんでしょ?
Which one is better?
どっちのほうがいいですか?
I used it.
使いました
But you want it, right?
でも欲しいんでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Put it out yourself and do it like this.
自分で出して、こうやって
He does this while moving the balls with his left hand.
左手で玉をさまさましながらしてくれる
I'll put it in again
また入れるんです
mosquito?
か?
Put your hand behind it.
その 後ろに手をついて
So, I took my legs.
で、足を取った
結構
What do you think?
どうですか?
My uncle is nervous.
おじさんが緊張して
Ah, it's out.
ああ、出た